Guide to the Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin) Jones Papers, 1903-1954
Department of Special Collections
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1921
  - Probate Orders
  - Progressives
  - Prohibition
  - Prostitution
  - Public Administrators
  - Public Ownership
  - Public Utilities
  - Pure Food
  - Railroadmen (Box 26, Folder 226)
  - Real Estate
  - Re-apportionment
  - Redwoods League
  - Rehabilitation, Industrial
  - Reporters, Court
  - Republican, The National
  - Revolver Laws
  - Re-apportionment. Legislature, 1921. (Box 26, Folder 227)
  - Fresno convention on reapportionment, December 17, 1921.
    Senator Jones appointed on committee to draft amendment to the State Constitution in re: restriction of representation in the State Senate. Folder includes correspondence (see: C.C. Young's opinion by request from Jones, Dec. 1921, under Reapportionment) and Jones notes written at the Fresno Convention.
  - Reorganization of the State Government of California. (Box 26, Folder 228)
  - Correspondence, filed by correspondent or subject
  - Social Insurance (Box 26, Folder 229)
  - Special Administrators
  - Stephens, Governor. Biennial Message
  - Syndicalism, criminal
  - Statuary, National Hall of
  - Supervisors
  - Sunday Laws
  - Taxes
  - Technology, Institute of
  - Torrens Land Act
  - Township, Santa Clara
  - Taxation, A-M, Correspondence and Reference Material (Box 26, Folder 230)
  - Taxation, N-Z (Box 26, Folder 231)
  - Taxation, Corporate: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Taxation, Corporate: Reference Material (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Uniform Conditional Sales Act (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Vivisection
  - Vaccination
  - Volstead Act and county enforcement ordinance (Prohibition Laws)
  - War Loan Organization
  - Water Development Act
  - Workmen's Compensation: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Workmen's Compensation: Reference Material (Box 27, Folder 236)
- INTERCESSION, 1922(filed by Correspondent's name)
  - Correspondence: A-G (Box 27, Folder 237)
  - Correspondence: H-Q (Box 27, Folder 238)
  - Correspondence: R-Z (Box 28, Folder 239)
  - Reference Materials: A-L (Box 28, Folder 240)
  - Reference Materials: M-Z (Box 28, Folder 241)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1923(filed by Correspondent's name)
  - A (Box 28, Folder 242)
  - B, January - February 1923 (Box 28, Folder 243)
  - March - May 1923 (Box 28, Folder 244)
  - C (Box 28, Folder 245)
  - D (Box 28, Folder 246)
  - EF (Box 28, Folder 247)
  - G (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - H (Box 29, Folder 249)
  - J (Box 29, Folder 250)
  - KL (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - M (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - NO (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - PQ (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - R (Box 30, Folder 255)
  - 1922 - February 1923 (Box 30, Folder 256)
  - S, March 1923 - 1924 (Box 30, Folder 257)
  - TUV (Box 30, Folder 258)
  - 1922 - February 1923 (Box 30, Folder 259)
  - W, March 1923 - 1924 (Box 30, Folder 260)
  - XYZ (Box 30, Folder 261)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1923
  - Aircraft (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Anonymous
  - Assessors
  - Banking (Box 30, Folder 263)
  - Barbers
  - Bible in Schools
  - Big Basin
  - Boxing
  - Building and Loan
  - Bar Association
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, Legislature, 1923
  - Budget, State of California, 1923-1925 (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - New Executive State Budget, prepared by Governor Richardson
  - Budget of Railroad Commission. Public Utilities corporations' report to Railroad Commission, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - Budget, Correspondence and Clippings (Box 31, Folder 266)
  - Budget, Amendments, etc. (Box 31, Folder 267)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 31, Folder 268)
  - Cemetery Removal
  - Charities and Corrections
  - Chattle Mortgages
  - Child Labor
  - Child Welfare
  - Christian Science
  - Colorado River Project
  - Consolidation
  - County Clerks
  - County Government
  - Courts
  - Clubs
  - Crimes
  - Community Property
  - Corporation Taxes
  - Claims and Bills (expenses) 1923 (Box 31, Folder 269)
  - Dairy Council (Box 31, Folder 270)
  - Deaf and Blind
  - Delinquent Women
  - Democracy
  - Dental Mechanics
  - Divorce
  - Domestic Court
  - Dredging
  - Education
  - Employment Agencies
  - Farming
  - Federal Practice Liens
  - Firecracker Prohibition
  - Fish and Game
  - Forests
  - Farming
  - Foot and Mouth Disease
  - Gasoline (Box 32, Folder 271)
  - Governmental Efficiency
  - Handbook, Legislature
  - Hetch Hetchy
  - Highway System
  - History Textbooks
  - Housing Shortage
  - Hichborn, Franklin
  - Illinois Constitution
  - Industrial Welfare Commission Report
  - Initiative Injunction
  - Insurance
  - Irish
  - Irrigation
  - Investigation, Witnesses
  - Japanese (Box 32, Folder 272)
  - Jury
  - Kindergarten Legislation
  - King Tax Bill
  - Klu Klux Klan - 1 clipping re: Clan in Oregon
  - Labor
  - Legislative Procedure
  - Lobbying
  - Loma Prieta Game Refuge
  - Lotteries
  - Masks, safety (Box 32, Folder 273)
  - Maternity
  - Medical
  - Mining
  - Minimum Wage Law
  - Miscellaneous, Legislature, 1923
  - Mother Lode Mine
  - Moving Pictures
  - Motor Vehicles, taxation of, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 274)
  - Correspondence, June 15, 1923 - October 29, 1924
  - National Economic League (Box 32, Folder 275)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Miscellaneous
  - Non-Partisan
  - Oil
  - Old Age Pension
  - Pacific Epileptic Colony (Box 32, Folder 276)
  - Partisanship
  - Part-Time Education
  - Pension
  - Picketing
  - Piute Pass Road
  - Pittsburgh Plus (steel)
  - Polytechnic School, California
  - Political Prisoners
  - Probation
  - Prohibition
  - Proportional Representation
  - Public Works
  - Purchasing
  - Popular Government
  - Power Companies-King Tax Bill
  - Railroad Commissioners (Box 32, Folder 277)
  - Real Estate
  - Republican Party
  - Revenue
  - Revolver Law
  - Roads
  - Reapportionment, Legislative Session, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Reapportionment. Correspondence June 1923 - July 1924 (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Farm Organizations Consideration of reapportionment
  - Organizations' correspondence with Senator Jones
  - Reapportionment. Correspondence, primarily Boggs and Clearly with Senator Jones, October 1923 - November 1924. (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Reapportionment. Drafts of amendments to Constitution, notes, clippings, miscellaneous. (Box 33, Folder 281)
  - Sabotage (Box 33, Folder 282)
  - Santa Clara Immigration District
  - Schools
  - Seals
  - Senate
  - Spoils System
  - Subsidized Officials
  - Supervisors, county
  - Surplus, Corporation
  - Taxation (Box 33, Folder 283)
  - Teachers' Agencies, Colleges, Pension
  - Tenure
  - Title Company
  - Tuberculosis
  - Vocational Training (Box 33, Folder 284)
  - Voting
  - Water and Power
  - Women's Relief Corps
  - Workmen's Compensation
  - Investigation Committee File, Legislature, 1923.Correspondence A-Z. (Box 33, Folder 285)
- INTERCESSION, 1924
  - Better America Federation (Less Government in Business) (Box 33, Folder 286)
  - Johnson, Hiram, Presidential Primary, 1924
  - Big Basin-Santa Cruz Stage Line (railroad) (Box 33, Folder 287)
  - Teapot Dome, newspaper clippings
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1925(filed according to name of Correspondent)
  - A (Box 33, Folder 288)
  - B (Box 33, Folder 289)
  - C: 1924 - February 1925 (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - C: March 1925 - 1926 (Box 34, Folder 291)
  - DE (Box 34, Folder 292)
  - F (Box 34, Folder 293)
  - G (Box 34, Folder 294)
  - H (Box 34, Folder 295)
  - IJ (Box 34, Folder 296)
  - K (Box 34, Folder 297)
  - L (Box 34, Folder 298)
  - M (Box 34, Folder 299)
  - NO (Box 34, Folder 300)
  - PQ (Box 34, Folder 301)
  - R (Box 34, Folder 302)
  - S (Box 35, Folder 303)
  - TUV (Box 35, Folder 304)
  - W: 1924 - February 1925 (Box 35, Folder 305)
  - W: March 1925 - 1926 (Box 35, Folder 306)
  - XYZ (Box 35, Folder 307)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1925(continued) - (filed by Subject Matter)
  - Accountants (Box 35, Folder 308)
  - Attaches
  - Bar Association (Box 35, Folder 309)
  - Bayshore Highway
  - Big Basin Road
  - Budget, 1925.For Progressives' fight on Budget of 1921 (1921-25) see file Budget, 1925.
  - Business Colleges, 1925
  - Child Labor (Box 35, Folder 310)
  - County Government
  - Education (SB 538) (Box 35, Folder 311)
  - Exemption, debtors (SB 164)
  - Fish and Game (Box 35, Folder 312)
  - Governorship, C.C. Young. Preliminary Correspondence, 1925-26 (Box 36, Folder 313)
  - Governorship. Miscellaneous clippings, 1925-26
  - Humane (AB 1263) Animal Trainer's Bill (Box 36, Folder 314)
  - Industrial Strikes (SB 64, AB 250)
  - Initiative. Assembly Constitutional Amendment no. 22., Senate Constitutional Amendment no. 8
  - Injunction
  - Jury
  - League of Women Voters, includes articles by Franklin Hichborn
  - Maps (Box 36, Folder 315)
  - Mortgage and Loans (SB 134, introduced by Senator Jones)
  - Motor Vehicle Act
  - Oleomargarine (Box 36, Folder 316)
  - Optometry
  - Parks, State
  - Prison labor
  - Reapportionment (SB 82220 introduced by Senators Jones, Boggs et.al.) (Box 36, Folder 317)
  - Reporters, Court
  - Syndicalism, Criminal
  - Torrens Land Title Law (SB 153) Senate Judiciary Committee
  - Workmen's Compensation (Box 36, Folder 318)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1925
  - A-B (Box 37, Folder 319)
  - C-D (Box 37, Folder 320)
  - E-H (Box 37, Folder 321)
  - I-L (Box 37, Folder 322)
  - M (Box 37, Folder 323)
  - N-Q (Box 38, Folder 324)
  - R-S (Box 38, Folder 325)
  - T (Box 38, Folder 326)
  - U-Z (Box 38, Folder 327)
- PROGRESSIVE VOTERS' LEAGUE, 1923-1926
  - Correspondence: AB (Box 38, Folder 328)
    Letters explaining background and nature of A/1 located at front of first folder (328)
  - Correspondence: C (Box 38, Folder 329)
    For explanation of origin, nature and aims of the Progressive Voters' League see: Benson, F.H. from Jones, August 17, 1923; correspondence Spreckles-Jones; L.M. Story to Jones, September 17, and September 23, 1925; invitation to initial meeting, to organize, written by Senator Jones (see: Progressive Voters' League folder August 18, 1925); Also, see: California Conference for Progressive Political Action, Report of meeting and who participated in it, March, 1924. For statement of principles of PVL see: PVL 1923-26, Publicity folder. Progressive Voters' League-organized August 25, 1923, to put into effect in California progressive and humanitarian legislation. Statement of Purpose of PVL, August 29, 1923. Senator Jones, President of PVL of California, 1925.
  - Correspondence: D-G (Box 39, Folder 330)
  - Correspondence: H, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 331)
  - Correspondence: H, 1924-26 (Box 39, Folder 332)
  - Correspondence: I-L (Box 39, Folder 333)
  - Correspondence: M-R (Box 39, Folder 334)
  - Correspondence: S-Z (Box 39, Folder 335)
  - Finance (Box 39, Folder 336)
  - Publicity (Box 39, Folder 337)
  - Miscellaneous, Elections, etc. (Box 40, Folder 338)
    Progressive Voters' League helped elect C.C. Young Governor in 1926. (See: Young, C.C. Governorship.)
- INTERSESSION, 1926
  - Political Campaign
    - Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 339)
    - Reference Material (Box 40, Folder 340)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 40, Folder 341)
    - AB (Box 40, Folder 342)
    - C-F (Box 41, Folder 343)
    - G-J (Hichborn, Franklin. Correspondence, includes booklet: Camouflage Organizations) (Box 41, Folder 344)
    - K-S (Box 41, Folder 345)
    - T-Z (Triple Falls Creek (Cartridge Creek), 1926.in re: U.S. Geographical Board naming Kings River points) (Box 41, Folder 346)
- LEGISLATIVE SESSION, 1927
  - AB (Box 41, Folder 347)
  - CDEFG (Box 41, Folder 348)
  - HIJ (Box 41, Folder 349)
  - K-Q (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - RS (Box 42, Folder 351)
  - TUVWXYZ (Box 42, Folder 352)
    Correspondence pertaining to current legislative business, filed by Subject Matter of the correspondence. Reference Material on a particular topic of legislation is henceforth filed with correspondence pertaining to the same topic; both correspondence and reference material, for example, beginning with A are filed in folders A.
  - A (Box 42, Folder 353)
    If there is not a large quantity of material or correspondence on a given topic, for instance a subject like peace, or Democracy, this material will not be placed in a folder by itself, but will be placed in the P or D folder of a given year, the beginning folder of each alphabetical section.
  - Accountants
  - Agriculture
  - Anatomy Bill (SB833)
  - Arbitration (AB 60) (Box 42, Folder 354)
  - Auto Liens (541, 459, 814, 815, 267, 268, 109)
  - Automobiles
  - Aviation (162, 201, 777, AB 1131)
  - B (Box 42, Folder 355)
  - Banks
  - Bar
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, Legislature, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Budget, State of California 1927(uniform) Budget Law for Counties (Box 43, Folder 357)
  - Building and Loan (Box 43, Folder 358)
  - C, Legislative Correspondence. Subject Matter, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 359)
  - Capital Punishment
  - Child Labor/Welfare
  - Community Property (Box 43, Folder 360)
  - Conway, Alden. Pacific Coast and Scenic Highway, Ind. 1927
  - County Government
  - Crime
  - D (Box 44, Folder 361)
  - Deciduous Fruit Station
  - E (Box 44, Folder 362)
  - Education
  - F (Box 44, Folder 363)
  - Feed
  - Firearms
  - Fireman
  - Fish and Game
  - Gas Tax (Box 44, Folder 364)
  - Gilbert, James Roy
  - Grade Crossings
  - H (Box 44, Folder 365)
  - Highways
  - I
  - Indeterminate Franchise
  - Inheritance Tax
  - Insurance
  - Judges (Box 44, Folder 366)
  - Judicial Council
  - Judiciary Committee, Senate
  - Judiciary Committee, Senate. Authors of Bills notified, 1927
  - Junior Colleges
  - Kindergarten (Box 44, Folder 367)
  - Kosher Meat
  - Labor
  - M (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Maps
  - Mutual Insurance (806)
  - Naturapaths (Box 45, Folder 369)
  - Newspapers (808)
  - Nurses
  - O (Box 45, Folder 370)
  - Palo Alto, Annexation
  - Parks and Park Commission
  - Part Time (568)
  - Prohibition
  - R (Box 45, Folder 371)
  - Redwood Park Commission
  - Religious Education
  - Slot Machines (Box 45, Folder 372)
  - Standardization
  - Statuary
  - Spiritualists
  - Stills, penalty for (SB 814, introduced by Senator Jones)
  - Supreme Court
  - Syndicalism (Box 45, Folder 373)
  - T (Box 46, Folder 374)
  - Taxation
  - Tenure
  - Tents
  - Title Company Recommendations
  - Toll Bridge
  - Ugufy (Box 46, Folder 375)
  - Veterans
  - W
  - Warehouse (523-525)
  - Young, C.C., Governor. Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 46, Folder 376)
- INTERSESSION, 1928(Correspondence by name of Correspondent)
  - Notes on session's legislation (Box 46, Folder 377)
  - A-G
  - H (Box 46, Folder 378)
  - I-M (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - N-V (Box 47, Folder 380)
  - W-Z (Box 47, Folder 381)
  - AB, After-Session Correspondence. Subject Matter (SM) (Box 47, Folder 382)
  - Bank of Italy, 1928
  - Bootleg, 1928
  - Building and Loan Material
  - Building and Loan Commission, 1928
  - CD, Aft-Sess Correspondence, SM, 1927-28 (Box 47, Folder 383)
  - Cooperative Associations
  - Cooperative Marketing, 1924-28
  - County Unit System of School Administration, 1927-28
  - EF, 1927-28 (Box 47, Folder 384)
  - Farmers
  - Farming, 27
  - G, 1928
  - HIJ, 1927-28 (Box 47, Folder 385)
  - Hoover, Herbert. Political Campaignk, 1928., Clippings
  - KIM, 1927-28 (Box 47, Folder 386)
  - NOPQ (Box 47, Folder 387)
  - Power Trust. Newspaper Clippings, 1928,and other data. (Box 48, Folder 388)
  - RS, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 389)
  - San Francisco Examiner. 1928-29, Clippings
  - T
  - Taxation. Solvent Credits, 1928
  - Tax Commission, in re: problem of rising cost of State Government, 1928. (Box 48, Folder 390)
  - Tax, Sales, 1927-28
  - VW
    Note: Some Main Issues in re: Legislation--past or future--in 1928:
    Banking Question and Foreclosures
    Heavy Mortgages
    Bank of Italy situation (see: Hichborn to Johnson, Hiram, February 3, 1928) in Hichborn folder.
    Ertrenched in power Transportation Companies, Banks and Utilities Companies
    Water--Assembly Constitutional Amendment no. 27 Taxation
    Taxation
- LEGISLATIVE SESSION, 1929(Legislative Correspondence, filed by name of Correspondent.)
  - ABC (Box 48, Folder 391)
  - A, 1929Legislative Correspondence
  - 1929
  - D-J (Hichborn, Franklin). Correspondence, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 392)
  - K-Q (Box 48, Folder 393)
  - R-Z (Box 48, Folder 394)
    1929 Legislative Session. Legislative Correspondence, filed according to Subject Matter. Correspondence is principally upon topics of legislation. It includes the months of 1928 just before the opening of 1929 Session.
  - A, legislative Correspondence, 1929,Subject Matter (Box 49, Folder 395)
  - B, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 396)
  - Banking, 1929.Includes material from 1924, 25, 26, 27, 28, on Banking. (Box 49, Folder 397)
  - Bar, State, 1929
  - Bills, copies of mailed to
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, Legislature, 1929
  - Building and Loan (Box 49, Folder 398)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 49, Folder 399)
    Explanatory Note for the Senate Cement Committee, 1929: The Material pertinent to the Special Senate Committee Created to Investigate an alleged Cement Trust in California is contained in the Three Manila Folders:
    (625) San Francisco Hearings, January 24, 25, 1929
    (626) Los Angles Hearing, February 4, 5, 6, 1929
    (627) Cement Committee-General Proceedings from origin to conclusion and Sacramento (final) Hearings, February 25, 1929.
    And in:
    The Grey-Fronted Volumes, I through V, containing the actual proceedings at the three hearings, and the booklets which contain the report of the Committee (see the Bibliography Card File and the Pamphlet Boxes, for 1929). For more information on the progress of the Cement Committee see folder: Sacramento Bee, Newspaper Clippings, 1929, and Newspapers Clippings, 1931. Also, see: letter Hichborn, Franklinn, to Jones, March 6, 1929
  - CC. Vol. I (Box 49, Folder 400)
  - Cement Committee. San Francisco Hearing. Correspondence, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 401)
  - Cement Committee. Los Angeles Hearings. Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 402)
  - Cement Committee. Sacramento Hearings (final hearings) and other material, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 403)
  - Cement Committee. Correspondence and Supplemental Report, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 404)
    Cement Committee:
    and see letter: Hichborn, Franklin to Jones, March 14, 1929 for Hichborn's personal observations on proceedings of Cement Committee. Also see Hichborn's letters of March 21, 1929 and March 27, 1929 to Jones.
  - Newspaper C lippings, miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 405)
  - Newspaper C lippings, miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 406)
  - Newspaper C lippings, miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 407)
  - Corporations, 1923-29 (Box 50, Folder 408)
  - County Unit (AB 459, in re: county elementary school system, 1929) (Box 51, Folder 409)
  - DE (Box 51, Folder 410)
  - Elections (SB 772), 1924-29
  - F,G, Grange, 1925-29 (Box 51, Folder 411)
  - H (Box 51, Folder 412)
  - Hardy Impeachment, 1929.State Superior Judge Carlos S. Hardy and Aimee Semple McPherson disappearance case. Trial in Senate.
  - I (Box 51, Folder 413)
  - Income Tax. Newspaper Clippings, 1929
  - J
  - Judges' Tenure, 1929.Senate Constitutional Amendment no. 3
  - Judiciary Committee, Senate, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 414)
  - Judiciary Committee, Correspondence. Folder no. 1, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 415)
  - Judiciary Committee, Correspondence. Folder no. 2, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 416)
  - Judiciary Committee, Requested Hearings, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 417)
  - KL, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 418)
  - Labor, 1929
  - Libel Laws, Civil Code, 1929
  - M (Box 52, Folder 419)
  - N
  - Narcotics. Newspaper Clippings, 1929.In re: State Aid in cure of dope addiction
  - O
  - PQ, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 420)
  - Palo Alto Times, February 19-27, 1929, Clippings (Box 52, Folder 421)
  - Palo Alto Times, 1929, Clippings
  - Poet Laureate of California, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 422)
  - Power Trusts. Correspondence of Hichborn, Franklin on
  - Power Trusts included. 1929
  - Prison Bill (women's prison, SB 169), 1929
  - Prohibition (see also: A for Anti-Saloon League correspondence for years during the 1920's), 1929. (Box 52, Folder 423)
  - Prohibition. Anti-Dry Sentiment, Volstead Law, etc. Newspaper Clippings, 1929.
  - Public Health (SB 813), 1929
  - RS, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 424)
  - Sewage Research (SB 651-652), 1929
  - Sacramento Union. 1929, Clippings
  - San Francisco Chronicle. 1929, Clippings
  - San Francisco Examiner. 1929, Clippings
  - San Jose Mercury Herald. 1929, Clippings
  - San Jose News. 1929, Clippings
  - T (Box 53, Folder 425)
  - Taxation
  - Taxation - Nelson Bill
  - Tax Commission, 1929-30 (Box 53, Folder 426)
  - (Box 53, Folder 428)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Taxation, 1929-30 (Box 53, Folder 429)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Taxation, 1929-30.Publications sent to H.C. Jones (postmarked January 1930) (Box 53, Folder 430)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Taxation, 1929-30.Publications mailed to Senator Jones (January, 1930) (Box 54, Folder 431)
  - Taxation, 1926-29 (Box 54, Folder 432)
  - Taxation, 1927-30 (Box 54, Folder 433)
  - U-Z (Box 54, Folder 434)
- INTERSESSION 1930(Correspondence filed primarily by correspondent)
  - A-F (Box 54, Folder 435)
  - G-J (Box 54, Folder 436)
  - K-Q (Box 55, Folder 437)
  - R-T (Box 55, Folder 438)
  - U-Z (Box 55, Folder 439)
- CORRESPONDENCE AND REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1930(Filed according to Subject Matter
  - Briggs, A.H. State Superintendent of California Anti-Saloon League, endorsement of candidates in 1930 Governorship Contest, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 440)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1921-30 (Box 55, Folder 441)
  - Congratulations to Senator Jones upon his reelection to State Senate, 1930
  - Clippings, newspaper, 1930
  - Daylight Saving, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 442)
  - Political Campaign: Senatorship, 1930.H.C. Jones, 18th Senatorial District. Newspaper Clippings. (Box 56, Folder 443)
  - Political Campaign: Senatorship, 1930.H.C. Jones, 18th Senatorial District. Clippings from County Newspapers. (Box 56, Folder 444)
  - Political Campaign: Senatorship, 1930.H.C. Jones, 18th Senatorial District. Correspondence, etc. (Box 56, Folder 445)
  - Political Campaign: Senatorship, 1930.H.C. Jones. Publicity. Elections on other issues, Correspondence and Clippings. (Box 56, Folder 446)
  - Political Campaign: Senatorship, H.C. Jones and Young, C.C. Governorship, 1930.San Jose Mercury Herald, Clippings (Box 56, Folder 447)
  - Political Campaign: Young, C.C., Folder no. 1 (Box 57, Folder 448)
  - Political Campaign: Governorship, C.C. Young. Folder no. 2 (Box 57, Folder 449)
  - Political Campaign: Governorship, Young. Folder no. 2 (Box 57, Folder 450)
  - Political Campaign: Governorship, Young. Folder no. 3 (Box 57, Folder 451)
  - Political Campaign: Governorship, Young. Folder no. 4
  - Political Campaign: Governorship, Young. Material from Young for Governor Headquarters, 1930.Folder no. 5 (Box 57, Folder 452)
  - Political Campaign: State Offices. Governorship, Senatorships, etc., 1930 (Box 57, Folder 453)
  - Pre-1931 Legislative Session Correspondence, 1930-31. (Box 58, Folder 454)
    Correspondence, A-Z. Correspondence pertains to the opening of the 1931 Legislative Session.
- LEGISLATIVE SESSION, 1931(Legislative Correspondence, filed according to name of Correspondent)
  - A, Legislative Correspondence, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 455)
  - A-B
  - B, 1931
  - CD, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 456)
  - C-L
  - M-S (Box 58, Folder 457)
  - T-Z (Box 58, Folder 458)
- LEGISLATIVE SESSION, 1931(Legislative Correspondence, filed according to Subject Letter.
  - A, Legislative Correspondence, Subject Matter (Box 58, Folder 459)
  - Adoption Bills, 1931(560-561) Department of Social Welfare, Miss Barry.
  - Adult Education, 1931
  - American-Jugoslav Defense, 1931
  - B, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 460)
  - Banking
  - Budget, State of California (Box 59, Folder 461)